NETFLIX PRESENTS
[TV presenter] Good afternoon.
This is a special program
with live updates relating
to the development of the now global
epidemic, pandemic, coronavirus.
The president is expected
to appear in a few minutes,
after an extraordinary
Council of Ministers
on the coronavirus crisis.
[President] Good afternoon,
my fellow citizens.
I can tell you that today,
I have informed the head of state
of tomorrow's
extraordinary Council of Ministers
to declare a state of alert
throughout our country, Spain,
that will last for the next 15 days.
[panting]
[siren approaching]
[siren stops]
What's wrong?
You okay?
[screams loudly]
DAY 1 OF LOCKDOWN
-[thunder crashes]
-[indistinct conversation]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[man coughing]
[García] What's her name?
[Castro] We don't know.
She hasn't said a word yet.
-What about fingerprints?
-We're working on it.
Your mother?
They won't let me see her.
Your boyfriend?
We're isolating.
[automated voice] Third floor.
[phone ringing]
Inspector, we have
the results of the fingerprints.
Her name is Saioa Blanco.
She's been missing
for nearly three months.
[doctor] She has binding marks
on her feet and hands.
And considering the state
of her eyes and body,
she must have been
locked up all this time.
Will she recover soon?
Well, we'll have to wait and see
what the neurologist has to say
and we'll have to find
a post-traumatic stress specialist.
[man] We're done.
I'll be downstairs.
Can I go in and see her?
Just one minute.
[monitors beeping]
Inspector Samuel García
from the local headquarters.
Agent Ramos, Agent Altuna.
They're the ones who found Saioa.
You should wear masks.
This virus is serious.
-[cell phone ringing]
-Excuse me.
-How is the girl?
-[Castro] Yeah.
Still in shock,
so we'll have to start
the investigation blind.
We've been given orders to make sure
that people don't breach the lockdown,
but if there is anything you need,
here is my card.
-Thank you.
-[Castro] Understood.
[cell phone chimes]
Emergency services received a call.
A driver spotted her
near the San Vicente intersection.
That's on the way to Picu Siana.
It's unbelievable.
We all thought she was dead.
Well, except for her mom.
She was the only one holding out hope.
[Agent Altuna] We should call her, right?
Yeah. Okay, fine. We'll do it.
[García] The case is ours
and so are the problems.
I didn't say anything.
Besides, we're going to
give her some good news.
She'll freak out when she sees her.
Her daughter is still alive.
She won't care about anything else.
[knocking on door]
[Julia] Who is it?
Inspector García and
Deputy Inspector Castro, National Police.
We need to talk to you.
Julia López?
Yeah.
Yeah… You find her?
We found her, yes.
She is alive.
[sobs softly]
How is she? Is she okay?
She had been kidnapped.
She'll need some time to recover,
but the important thing is she is alive.
Okay.
[Julia sobbing]
[nurse] Put your mask on.
[monitors beeping]
[Julia cries softly]
[sobbing] My love.
Oh, my love.
With the state of alert at this time,
I'll need all available staff
at my disposal.
So this case will have to be dealt with
by you two.
Fuck, it's like the end of the world.
[García] Maybe it is.
-[Castro] See you tomorrow.
-See you tomorrow.
[TV presenter] …continue to arrive
at the Gijón fairgrounds.
Its central pavilion is being fitted out
as a field hospital
in case it becomes necessary…
Carlos?
-Hello.
Are you okay?
I have a slight fever and I'm coughing.
-Shit.
-Don't worry. I'm fine.
How about you?
[Castro] Well…
We have a case.
[parking brake clicks]
[sighs]
RETIREMENT HOME
[knocking on window]
Mom.
[woman speaking Spanish indistinctly]
DAY 2 OF LOCKDOWN
[Castro] She disappeared on 20th December.
She left home on her bike
early in the morning.
The bike was found in a ditch,
but no trace of her.
They investigated those close to her,
local criminals, but there was nothing.
We'll have to start from scratch.
There, that's San Vicente intersection.
Don't worry, it won't rain.
Besides, spring is just four days away.
So? It rains as much
in spring here as winter.
Let's head up.
Police!
Stop, police!
Stop!
Freeze!
Hey, relax, relax.
Get down! On your knees!
[both grunting]
[Castro panting]
[panting]
It's for personal consumption.
There's nothing to do here.
We've got more important things to do.
Fucking hippies.
[cell phone ringing]
Yeah?
-Saioa's woken up.
-Let's go.
[Castro grunts softly]
-[monitors beeping]
-[door opens]
[Nogueira] They're here.
Hi, there. Paz Nogueira,
from the IMA Center
for Post-Traumatic Stress.
-Inspector García.
-Deputy Inspector Castro.
How is the girl doing?
She's weak, but she's recognized her mom
and a connection was made instantly.
When will she be able to speak?
It could be a matter of hours or months.
Yeah.
Doctor, if the girl says or draws
anything, it would be of great help.
The last thing we should do now
is to force her to remember
what she went through.
I know it's delicate,
but her kidnapper could disappear.
Or he may even kidnap another girl.
We have to make her feel safe,
only then will she dare to speak.
How long do you think
it'll take you to do it?
I don't know,
but her mom and I will do everything
we can do to help you, honestly.
-Well, thanks a lot.
-[indistinct announcements over PA]
-What about the girl's father?
-He died in a mine.
-Her stepfather was the main suspect.
-How come?
They got divorced
shortly before the girl disappeared.
Let's pay him a visit.
[indistinct conversation]
Do whatever the hell you want.
[García] Ricardo Marquina?
Damn, the thing about Saioa is true!
She appeared, right?
Come on, I can tell from here
that you two are a bunch of dirty coppers.
How is the girl?
She's fine, she's alive.
Holy shit, dude, I can't believe it.
Tell me, how is Julia?
Taking it in.
So what is it you want?
I've already been investigated,
your colleagues were here
a number of times
and they searched absolutely everything.
We've heard that you and Saioa
didn't get along too well.
Here we go again.
I was her stepfather,
she was a stroppy teenager,
needless to say, we didn't get along.
To get to the point,
I hated the girl to death,
but on my fucking life,
let's make it very clear,
hand on my heart,
I never laid a hand on that girl.
Okay?
So, if you don't have a warrant
and there's nothing else,
I've enough on my plate to get on with.
-[engine revving]
-[tools clattering]
[indistinct conversation]
Here.
Morning.
What's wrong?
Did you know that some of the force
are placing bets on you?
-Seriously?
-Mmm-hmm.
And how are the stakes going?
Most think you'll mess it up
before Easter.
-That's in less than a month.
-Things are getting exciting, then.
And how much did you bet?
You said it was over
and I take your word for it.
Look at this. Last week,
a Korean woman in St. James Way
reported him
for trying to force her into his SUV.
Manuel Gómez, known as the "Dog Killer."
Look where he lives.
That's next to the intersection.
Yeah.
[exhales]
[dog barking]
[Castro gasps] Fuck!
Quiet! Shut up!
Shh! Just… That's enough!
Shh!
Well, go on.
[shushing] Go on. In your kennel.
No one's here.
-Let's go inside and take a look.
-Are you sure?
[grunts]
There's a bed in there.
[gun fires]
What the fuck are you doing in my house?
Get out of here!
-Police!
-Drop the gun!
Put the shotgun down!
[dog barking]
What are you doing in my house?
Calm down. We're looking for a suspect.
We think
he might have been hiding in here.
In my stables?
[Castro] Yes. Mind if we take a look?
[García] It'll just be a moment.
[Castro] Give me the gun.
There's nobody here.
And the bed, the food?
Oh, that.
That's my cousin's.
He stays here when we go hunting.
Ah, he was always a bit dirty,
that bastard.
-I assume you have a gun permit.
-Of course.
What do you work as?
-Who? Me?
-Yeah.
I used to check the water meters
of the houses in the county,
but the company filed a case
and now I'm unemployed.
Last week, you were
reported for assaulting a girl.
-Why do you say that?
-Tell us what happened.
You think I did something?
Fuck, there was a misunderstanding.
I was in Oviedo, drinking.
And on my way home,
I saw the lass and I stopped.
I chatted her up and she followed my lead.
I thought she wanted something else.
I tried to get a feel, but…
But she went crazy.
I really didn't want to do anything.
Just wanted to get laid. [chuckles]
[Castro] We should arrest him
for being a pig.
Fucking disgusting.
[cell phone ringing]
Speak to me. Give me a sec.
Right, I just got it.
The forensic report.
"No traces of DNA found,
and the wound on her leg was identified
as a bite from a dog."
What else?
"The grains of sand
under her fingernails belong to…"
"They contain traces of ethanol
and tartaric acid."
-[brakes screeching]
-What are you doing?
-Wine contains ethanol and tartaric acid.
-So?
Those stables were full of vats of wine.
He's gone.
What a son of a bitch.
Call the station.
There's police everywhere,
he can't be far away.
We have a suspect on the run.
He just escaped
in a red Mitsubishi Montero.
I'll send our location.
Castro!
[grunting]
[García panting]
[softly] Castro.
[Castro] Oh, shit.
[both sniffing]
[Castro groans, exhales]
[cell phone ringing]
Samuel, please…
[coughing]
Yes?
[retching]
We're on our way.
[siren wailing]
-Call an ambulance now, please.
-I'll be back. Stay calm.
Here!
Quick.
What happened?
He tried to jump the checkpoint
and went over the edge.
[thunder rumbling]
-[García] What do we know?
-[officer] There's nobody there.
[García] He's wounded.
[Castro] He can't be far.
[thunder crashing]
-[gun fires]
-[Castro] Fuck!
[breathing heavily]
[García] Come on, drop the shotgun!
Drop it!
Drop the shotgun!
-[Castro] Drop the gun, damn it!
-Look at me, it's over!
[Castro] Drop it!
This is just the beginning.
[Castro] Drop the gun!
This is just the beginning!
-[Castro] No
-No!
[thunder crashes]
Fuck!
DAY 3 OF LOCKDOWN
[indistinct conversation over radio]
[siren wailing in distance]
[camera shutter clicks]
How are you?
You should see this.
They were in the wine cellar.
And they're different sizes.
He didn't act alone.
He mentioned a cousin.
He said they went hunting together
on the weekends.
Get the cousin. We need to find out
if there'll be more girls.
We must close the case
before the press gets wind of this
and makes this even more difficult.
The press is busy with the virus.
Yeah, but in small towns like this,
rumors fly.
[García sighs]
One left. Then to the right…
-Sure, take one every six hours.
-[García] Are there any signs on the way?
-No, but it's the only house there.
-Thank you.
Yes, this is a mess, it's pretty big.
I'll tell you later.
If it gets to 39,
tell me and I'll take you to ER.
Okay, bye.
Try to get some rest, all right?
We'll talk again later.
Me too. So much.
-I can drive you home if you want.
-No, don't worry.
You could use some rest.
I'll rest when you rest.
The Dog Killer's cousin has a farm
a couple of kilometers from here.
[engine starts]
[cows mooing]
[García] Morning.
Morning.
We've been told this is
Manuel Gómez's cousin's cow farm.
Is that you?
Has he messed up again?
We talked to him
and he said he goes hunting with you
on the weekends. Is that true?
I've never hunted in my life.
And if I was to hunt,
my cousin would be the last person
I would go with.
-You don't get along?
-We don't get along. Period.
He goes out hunting with the Demon.
A crazy guy who gets high on everything.
He spent some years in the Legion.
Do you know where he is now?
He works for his brother, driving a truck.
At the Marquina workshop.
He lives right there, in the back,
in an old caravan. [chuckles dryly]
Thanks very much.
Hey!
Be careful, okay? Don't trust him.
He is a bad apple, that one.
[siren wailing]
[officer on phone]
The phone number 672-274-575
belongs to Santiago Marquina.
The last call from the Dog Killer's phone
was to Santiago Marquina.
[García] The Demon.
Going in?
[Castro] The door is open.
-[beeping]
-[gas hissing]
Holy shit! Get back!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
[coughs]
[both panting, grunting]
[siren wailing]
He was expecting us.
[Agent Ramos] What the hell happened?
Officer, we're in charge
of the investigation.
-And who are you?
-Commissioner Basterra.
Commissioner. We can be of great help.
We all know each other here.
Thank you, but we would appreciate it
if you make sure
nobody breaches the perimeter.
He's right. Everyone knows everyone
in these small towns.
I do not want the press to find out about
what is going on until we catch this guy.
So, the less they know, the better.
He spent six months in Iraq in 2004.
He was discharged and was given therapy.
He has priors for disorderly conduct,
drug possession, and assault.
What a guy!
[indistinct conversation]
[coughs]
[indistinct conversation over radio]
Commissioner.
[Commissioner Basterra] Hang on.
These two are boys.
This is not what we thought it was.
[Commissioner Basterra exhales]
Go and get some rest.
No. We need to find that son of a bitch.
Marta, you've been up
for the last 48 hours.
First thing tomorrow, we'll analyze this
together calmly and organize the search.
What if those kids are still alive?
Go and rest. I need a clear head
on you both tomorrow.
[Commissioner Basterra sighs]
[Martha mumbling]
Relax. Everything will be all right, okay?
Can I go with him?
You must self-isolate at home for 14 days.
It's the protocol.
I'm police. I'm on an important case.
You are a close contact.
No, he was isolated
and we were social distancing, damn it.
I'm sorry, but you must self-isolate.
[sighs]
No class. Fortnite all days.
What about you, Eva?
-So boring.
-She's on her phone all day.
-That's not true.
-You're on Instagram all the time.
-Don't listen to him.
-[Pilar] Dinner's ready!
-See you, Dad.
-Bye.
-I love you.
-I love you too, baby.
-Is it really that serious?
-The virus?
Hmm.
So it seems. I think it's best
if they stay with you for now.
Sure, that's not a problem.
Thank you.
How are you holding up?
Holding up. If it gets too much,
I start cleaning shoes.
Ah, good.
I miss you all.
-Take care.
-[laptop chimes]
DAY 4 OF LOCKDOWN
[woman on radio] …are now ready
to manufacture on a large scale
to make medically-approved face masks.
They expect to have
the certificate by next week and…
-[siren wailing]
-[exhales]
I'm sorry.
[García] How is Carlos?
He was admitted. He wasn't breathing well.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm perfectly fine.
Carlos is strong.
He'll be out soon, you'll see.
-[knocks on door]
-[Commissioner Basterra] Come in.
We've already identified the other four.
The kidnappings occurred
in different areas of Spain,
so no one would link the cases.
This girl was the first victim.
She disappeared in León 15 months ago.
Santander, 12 months ago.
Lugo, nine months ago.
Palencia, six months ago.
And Saioa Blanco, who disappeared
in December and is the only local one.
One kidnapping every three months.
The sexual motive is still an option,
but all of this
bears the mark of a ritual.
The nightdresses, the crowns, the dolls,
and this mark here
that Saioa has on her back.
-[sighs] Have the families been told?
-No.
We're keeping all of this
under wraps for another 48 hours.
I wish I could tell them
that we have found their children.
Or, at least, their kidnappers.
So we have 48 hours left.
Commissioner.
The Demon's truck has appeared.
Wait.
Use them.
[sighs]
MISSING
SUSPECT 1 - SUSPECT 2
[siren wailing]
-Good morning.
-[García] Morning.
-We haven't touched anything.
-Thank you, we'll take care of it.
Be careful.
[grunts softly]
[grunting]
Son of a bitch.
[Castro] Oh, shit.
He's a hunter and he knows the area.
He can't be far off.
It'll be like finding
a needle in a haystack.
Let's go see his brother.
Thank you.
See you later.
[siren wailing]
What's wrong?
The thing about Saioa and the Demon
is all over social media.
You know what?
I'm starting to get sick of the police.
[García] Where can we find your brother?
My dear friend,
that would be the million-dollar question.
I wish I knew.
I've been ringing him all morning
and he won't pick up my calls.
You have no idea where he could be?
Not even of somewhere he could hide?
That sounds like it's your job, guys.
I'm only his brother.
I'm not his guardian angel.
Hey! Hey!
Your brother is suspected
of kidnapping five teenagers!
Either you tell me what you know
or I'll charge you with collusion.
Let me go now.
There's a hermitage in the mountains
next to a fountain called Cuervo Fountain.
He used to take his dates up there.
Unfortunately, that's all I have for you.
Hey, gorgeous…
tell your partner
that he needs to calm down.
[Castro exhales]
The hermitage is here.
And here's where they found the truck.
-[gun fires]
-[grunts]
-[yelling]
-[guns firing]
[gun clicking]
[yells in frustration]
Shit.
[grunts, exhales]
[panting]
-[guns continue firing]
-[breathing heavily]
[gun clicking]
[Demon] I'm out of bullets.
-I'm out of bullets!
-Hold your fire!
[Demon] I'm out of bullets!
Here I am, you fucking bunch of twats.
[García] Get down!
[Demon] Make me.
Get down!
Lie down.
[Demon] Come and make me.
-Lie down now!
-No.
Huh?
-Lie down.
-I don't want to.
[Castro] Bastard!
[Demon grunts] You son of a bitch!
You son of a bitch!
I'm gonna kill you!
It's over.
No. This is just the beginning.
-Take him away.
-This is just the beginning!
This is just the beginning! [laughs]
This is just the beginning,
you hear me? [grunts]
[García sighs] Jesus.
[siren wailing]
-[keys jangling]
-[lock opening]
[door closes]
I won't tell you anything.
So enough of the theatrics.
Don't worry.
We don't need you to say anything.
We have plenty of evidence.
That's fantastic.
You're gonna be the first person
in this area
to get a full-term life sentence.
You were at the hermitage.
-Crazy stuff, right?
-[clicks tongue]
You're not crazy. Just fucking sick.
No… We are not sick,
it's the society that is sick,
or haven't you seen
what's going on out there?
The pandemic?
The end of the world.
Yeah.
So that's why
you kidnapped all those kids.
Uh-huh.
Someone had to do something
to appease the thunderous Taranis.
The Almighty. The God of Storms.
What have you done with the kids?
Where are you holding them?
I told you
that someone had to appease Taranis.
What happened to Saioa?
Were you going to sacrifice her too?
It was only a few days away,
but the Dog Killer
couldn't follow the rules.
Somehow, the asshole took her out
to get some fresh air
and the girl ran away from us.
Otherwise you would have never found jack.
-So you were the one making the rules.
-No!
-No?
-Not I.
All this is the work of the Prophet.
Who is the Prophet?
He is the one who guides.
And he is very smart.
You will never catch him.
Listen to me.
Now then, you have the chance
to be smarter than him right now.
If you tell me his name,
the full life sentence will fall on him
and not you.
Well, now you've caught me,
I must bear that cross.
Tell me his name! Tell me his name.
Hit me. Hit me. Hit me.
Maybe that way
you'll get me to tell you something.
Come on. Hit me.
Hit me.
Come on. Come on.
By the way,
you should know the Prophet
has not completed his masterpiece yet,
so keep your eyes open.
[door opens and closes]
[García sighs] Did you hear that?
It's a bluff.
He's not smart enough for that,
I don't think.
There's only one person that can help us.
[sirens wailing]
[door opens]
-How is she?
-Better.
We have two suspects.
One committed suicide,
the other is in custody.
[exhales deeply]
I would like to show some pictures
to your daughter, if I may,
to confirm it's them.
It's too soon,
I don't think she's ready for it.
I know, but it's very important.
There may be a third party involved,
and we need to confirm this.
[exhales sharply]
I don't know.
We need to prevent him
from hurting another girl again.
[exhales shakily]
If she sees you come in, she'll be scared.
Thank you.
Oh, my darling.
[monitors beeping]
How are you?
My love…
Was it them?
These men have already been caught, okay?
We want…
[Nogueira] It's fine.
How many were there, Saioa?
SAN RAFAEL HOSPITAL
EMERGENCY
How is Carlos?
He was put on a ventilator.
And they say that he should
start to improve in a matter of hours.
I'm sure he will.
Did you talk to the girl?
Fuck's sake.
What now?
We need to find him before he acts again.
[engine starts]
[thunder rumbling]
[assistant] Taranis was referred to
as the god of storms and tempests.
They made human sacrifices to appease him
during the summer and winter solstices,
or the spring and autumn equinoxes.
Every three months.
The straw dolls, the mistletoe,
the symbols, the ritual sacrifices…
All of that is from Celtic mythology,
from the Druid world.
[assistant] Druids were priests
with prophetic powers in Celtic Europe.
They performed human sacrifices
and believed in reincarnation.
So, in short,
we are dealing with a chosen one,
a fucking psychopath who thinks
that he needs to do human sacrifices
to appease the wrath of the gods
before the end of the world.
It'll be spring in 48 hours.
[Commissioner Basterra] We have 48 hours.
-[thunder rumbling]
-Oh, this is crazy.
We have two full floors
and they say this is just the beginning.
By the way, did you hear about this girl?
Yeah, a friend from the ICU said
she's been held hostage for several months
and the police arrested some local.
I know, that's scary…
[Castro] Yes, I just received them,
both of them.
Yes, I have both lists here.
I see that number keeps coming up on
the Dog Killer's and the Demon's phones.
Give me the info.
[García sniffs]
-Let's see.
-[pencil scribbling]
Yeah, I can see it.
The number is from a prepaid card.
Okay, thank you.
[cell phone taps on table]
Look at this.
The Demon and the Dog Killer
knew each other since they were kids.
[Castro] Shit.
[García exhales deeply]
[Castro] The number belongs to
one Ismael Fernández,
who, in 2015, passed away.
He's not a madman.
He knows exactly what he's doing.
[Castro sighs]
[click tongue]
How can people be so…
We'll catch him.
I'm gonna get a coffee.
-Want one?
-No, thank you.
[exhales deeply]
[exhales]
Can I help you?
Hello?
Hey, wait.
Wait, stop.
Stop!
Stop, police!
[panting]
Turn around now. Slowly.
The hood.
Show me your ID. Hand your documents over.
Why were you in front of the station?
Didn't you hear the news?
There is a curfew.
You can't be on the streets.
SURNAME - VEGA
NAME - LIDIA
Just go back home.
[sirens wailing in distance]
[Castro sighs]
-Who was that?
-No one. A mad girl.
[Castro exhales deeply]
DAY 5 OF LOCKDOWN
[phone ringing]
-[sirens wailing in distance]
-[clicks tongue, exhales]
[grunts softly]
[exhales deeply]
[exhales, sniffs]
MY MUM HAS PASSED AWAY
-Samuel, I'm sorry.
-Where is she?
It's a disaster. So many were sick and
they didn't let us take 'em to Emergency.
Where is she?
Our order is to take them to the morgue.
-I want to see her.
-They won't let us.
Samuel!
[man] Excuse me, you can't be here!
Did you hear me?
Get out of my fucking way.
Get out!
-[banging on coffin]
-[sobbing]
[cell phone ringing]
Hello.
I'm on my way.
-[indistinct conversation over radio]
-Take them to the lab.
[camera shutters clicking]
[siren wailing]
I'm really sorry, Samuel.
What do we know?
She is a nurse, 20 years old.
She was talking to her friend
when someone attacked her
and took her away in her own car,
a gray Peugeot 308.
-Any CCTV?
-Yes.
There's one at the main entrance
and one on the corner.
I've asked for the images.
Do you think it was him?
That zip tie is just like
the ones we found in the truck.
-Come with me.
-Where to?
[engine starts, revs]
[siren wails]
-What happened?
-A girl has been kidnapped.
[indistinct conversation]
Commissioner?
He's at the Government Delegation
for a pandemic follow-up meeting.
We need the prisoner to be present
at a search.
Have you talked to the judge yet?
Call him and ask for authorization.
Samuel, are you sure?
We can't waste any more time.
Where are we going?
Stay here.
[Demon grunts]
What's wrong now? Do you want details?
Who is the Prophet? Tell us the name.
[laughs softly]
You had to hear their screams.
Like when you shoot a deer
and it gets badly wounded.
They were just the same.
[both grunt]
[coughing, groaning]
Who is the Prophet? Tell me his name.
And the boys, they were the ones
with the loudest screams.
[groaning]
Tell us his name
or you won't get out of here alive.
You don't have the balls for this.
[choking]
Tell us his name.
Tell me his name.
Who is the Prophet?
Who is the Prophet? Tell me.
Tell me his name.
Tell me the name. Tell me his name!
Who is the Prophet? Tell me his name!
Tell me his name!
[choking, gasping]
[coughing]
I'll never tell you his name.
Samuel.
You can leave if you want.
Who is the Prophet?
If you do it, it will ruin you.
I'll say you tried to escape.
I'll take my chances.
Come on.
-[gun cocks, fires]
-[Demon groans]
-Stop! What the fuck are you doing?
-Let go of me! Let go of me!
Stay out!
[laughing softly]
The name.
The fucking name!
You've actually got a pair.
Three, two…
one!
Samuel!
The hell are you doing?
A life is at stake. I had to at least try!
You're suspended immediately
without salary.
[García breathing heavily]
I cannot protect you any longer.
[Demon laughing softly]
[sirens wailing]
We need to try to do more
because we can't just be idle bystanders.
We spoke to her
and said there were three men.
Surely she can give us
some more information.
Don't you think my daughter
has suffered enough?
Julia, another girl has been kidnapped.
Look, I'm deeply sorry,
but Saioa needs to forget what happened,
not to remember it again.
-Don't you realize that that girl--
-Listen, Paz, stop! It's over!
-Leave my daughter alone, will you?
-Julia…
[monitors beeping]
[sirens wailing in distance]
URGENT
MISSING
[laptop chimes]
-[phones ringing]
-[indistinct conversation]
How is he?
Well, we have transferred him
to the ICU as a precaution.
With the ventilator and new medication,
we hope that he will stabilize
and start improving.
-May I see him?
-Sorry.
Just a minute so he knows I'm here.
I'm sorry, it's protocol.
Please, let me see him.
Don't worry,
I'll let him know that you were here.
[sighs]
Don't worry, he's in good hands.
I'm sorry.
[cell phone chimes]
PAZ NOGUEIRA - Can we talk?
Police.
Ramos.
Inspector.
I need your help.
Do you know this man?
This photo must've been taken
20 or 25 years ago.
Of course I do.
They called him "the Prophet".
Kids loved him.
Okay. Do you know
where we can find him right now?
I haven't heard of him for many years,
but his father lives near Infiesto.
Thank you.
Wait, wait! I know the area very well.
I'll take you there. Come on.
[siren wailing in distance]
[Nogueira] Inspector…
Inspector.
What do you want?
I don't know,
maybe it has nothing to do with it,
but I've seen the cuts on Saioa's back.
A woman under treatment at our center
has the same symbol engraved on her chest.
She was in a cult when she was young.
What's the name of the woman?
Lidia Vega.
Shit.
[bell tolling]
[Agent Ramos] It's on the outskirts.
-Hello, Lidia.
-Hello.
You well?
That coffee smells nice.
Do you want one?
I could really use one.
[thunder rumbling]
[dogs barking in distance]
[cell phone chimes]
SAMUEL - I have a suspect
I'm on my way to Infiesto with Ramos
SAMUEL
LOCATION
There's a car here.
It's the car of the girl
who disappeared yesterday.
I was 17 years old.
I had run away from home and lived
with some hippies in an abandoned mine.
We spent all day
smoking weed and having sex.
Until the guru of it all began to get
obsessed with druids and sacrifices.
[Castro] What was the guru's name?
He was called "the Prophet".
What happened?
[Agent Ramos] That was his father.
He wanted to perform a ritual on me.
Good thing one of the guys
stopped him in time.
[thunder rumbling]
[García gasping]
[Castro] Who was the Prophet?
What was his name?
His last name was Ramos.
He came from Infiesto.
[breathing heavily, retching]
[cell phone ringing]
Yes?
[Castro] Samuel, it's him.
Officer Ramos is the Prophet.
[García whimpering]
[sirens wailing]
[line ringing]
Pick up. Pick up. Come on, pick up.
[thunder rumbling]
Samuel!
-Samuel.
-[officers speaking indistinctly]
Samuel.
[officer] Inspector!
Inspector.
There's a corpse inside.
It must have been dead for years.
[alarm ringing]
-What's that noise?
-It's an alarm.
There is a mine down there.
DAY 6 OF LOCKDOWN
[alarm rings]
-[alarm rings]
-[metal thudding]
[alarm rings]
[grunts softly, exhales]
[breathing heavily]
[rats squeaking]
[woman screaming in distance]
[screaming continues]
-[guns firing]
-[Castro gasping]
[panting]
[woman continues screaming]
-[grunts]
-[gun clicking]
[Agent Ramos] I am the Prophet!
I know the destiny of men!
[woman moaning, crying]
[woman screaming]
[Castro grunts]
[grunts]
[woman continues moaning]
[woman gasping, moaning]
Relax.
-[woman gasping]
-Relax.
[woman crying]
-[muffled] Behind you!
[woman screaming]
[Castro coughing]
[woman continues screaming]
[gasping]
[coughs]
[wailing]
A prophecy is being fulfilled.
It's the end of the world.
[woman, muffled] No! No!
[alarm rings]
[breathing heavily]
Don't move.
Don't move, I said!
This is just the beginning.
-[panting]
-[woman gasping]
[woman whimpering]
DAY 10 OF LOCKDOWN
[TV presenter]
At two o'clock in the morning,
Congress authorized the extension
of the state of alert
until April 11th.
It had been 20 years since
a plenary session had been so long.
With 321 votes in favor,
none against, and 28 abstentions,
Congress authorized
the extension of the state of alert.
Confinement measures…
How is the girl?
Better.
Does it hurt?
No. I'm all right.
How is Samuel's family?
You can imagine.
I missed you so much.
So did I.
[sirens wailing in distance]
[TV presenter] …that is just an example
of what is starting to happen
in many hospitals in the region.
There have been 1,720 deaths
due to coronavirus in our country.
That is an increase
of 394 since yesterday.
According to the latest counts,
the number of infected people
amounts to 28,527.
[Carlos] Fuck.
It's like the end of the world.
Maybe it is.